# Vasyl Miskiv

# Frontend developer

+38 063 827 09 72 | Telegram Gmail | LinkedIn | Skype Github 1 | Github 2 Kyiv, Ukraine Ready to work remotely

# **Summary**

Frontend developer with more than one year of commercial experience developing SPA and full-stack MERN web applications. Mainly developed MVP applications, including CRM system, webmail, portal, and other web services for one of the top ISP companies from the US. Maintained legacy code on different projects, fixed bugs, and implemented new functionality on projects which were written from scratch. Conducted business correspondence with teams from the US.

## **Skills**

- Languages: Typescript, Javascript, GraphQL HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Libraries: React.is, Redux, Redux-thunk, Vuex, RxJs, NgRx, MobX, Axios, Uuid, Bcrypt, Jwt, Nodemon, Concurrently, Ramda, Yup, Formik, Styled-components, Socket.io, Chart.js
- Frameworks: Vue, Angular 2, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Express.js, Nest.js
- Uls: Bootstrap, Material UI
- **ORMs:** Sequelize, Mongoose, TypeOrm, Prisma
- **DBs:** PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Tools: Git, Postman, React/redux devtools, Pixel perfect, MongoDB compass, Gulp, Webpack, Eslint
- Repositories: Bitbucket, Gitlab, Github
- Cloud platforms: Heroku, Vercel, Netlify, Render
- Other: Rest API, OOP, BEM
- Tracking systems: Jira
- English: B2 | Upper-Intermediate

# **Experience**

#### Frontend developer at Inquire (EarthLink.net) 06/2022 - 12/2022

Tech stack: Javascript, Typescript, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, Axios, GraphQL, Ramda, REST API, TailwindCSS, Styled-components

Responsibilities: debug, maintain existing legacy code, code review, develop and implement features to web applications according to CI/CD, conduct business correspondence with teams and customers from the US

## Frontend developer self-employed 11/2021 - 06/2022

Tech stack: Javascript, Typescript, React, Redux, Vue.js, Vuex, Axios, REST API, Styled-components Responsibilities: debug, develop, implement new functionality

Accounting manager, audit assistant at Innova consulting group 09/2017 - 11/2021

Responsibilities: accounting services, taxation, audit, data processing management

### **Education**

## **Open International University of Human Development "Ukraine"**

Master's degree in Accounting and taxation

#### Self-education

- MDN web docs
- Codewars.com

- Leetcode.com
- Udemy.com

#### **Achievements**

Codewars: 4th kvu

Typing speed: 80+ wpm